[Music]
wo y'all going to make me lose my mind
up in here up in here y'all going to
make me go all out up in here up in here
y'all going to make me act the fool up
in here
up in here going make me lose my up in
here up in here from the historic
Lincoln Theater in Washington DC Dave
Chappelle thank
you thank you thank you oh
yeah oh yeah
all right oh
really
boy y make it good to come home boy I
swear I know man it's been a while it's
been a
while DC is
different I've been gone man took me
years to be able to do this show boy DC
has changed it's different
nails
there a lot of white people walking
around is
it I mean I left I left DC in the 80s it
was it was not like this in the 80s when
crack was going on remember when crack
was going on why people be looking at DC
from Virginia with binoculars and
[__] well that looks
dangerous not yet
yet new white people you Can't Scare
these white people I
tried roll up on them
Boo the hell is wrong with
you those days are
over I'm glad that you know like we
doing a show here by Howard you know and
you see like white people come out and
that's good one thing I'm
seeing you'll be walking down the street
and you'll see like a group of black
dudes walking not just any old black
dude we talking you know
thugs talking you know it be some Thugs
and in a group in a group they got like
one or two sometimes as many as three
white guys to be with them you ever seen
this
[__] let me tell you something about
those white
guys those white guys are the most
dangerous [__] in them
groups well it's
true it's true man it ain't no telling
what they've done to get them black
dudes
respect well them black dudes have seen
them do some wild [__] I'll tell you
that I been trying to tell brothers that
every every group of brothers should
have at least one white guy in it I'm
serious for
safety cuz when the [__] goes
down somebody's going to need to talk to
the
police
I mean that's when that that's when that
white friend comes in
handy uh-oh Ernie you want to get this
one come on now come on now do something
so black people are very afraid of the
police that is a big part of our culture
don't matter how rich you are how old
you
are we just afraid of them we got we got
every reason to be afraid of them you
know what I mean like you're a white
lady you ever been pulled over before
you know no what they say let me see
your driver's license and your
registration right see see I'm just
guessing that's not what they say to
us you wouldn't believe what they say to
us spread your cheeks and lift your sack
like what the
[__] excuse me you heard me spread open
your cheeks and lift your
sack I got a driver's license
too there easier ways to prove who I am
and [__] what does that Pro prove I
can't go to the bank like that cash my
check what do you mean you don't have
any ID wait a
minute
oh oh I'm sorry Mr Chappelle right this
way why didn't you spread your cheeks in
the
beginning scared of
them I'm serious man you ever be a red
light the police might pull up next to
you it won't be no big deal for you but
you know what I [__] fall apart oh oh
[__] oh don't look over
there but I didn't always know that was
a black thing it took me a while to
figure that out I learn I learned that
[__] in New York I was in New York
City now I was hanging out with a friend
of mine he was a white guy you know we
were just hanging out and we were lost
in the city you know we were smoking a
Dr
now I don't know if it's a coincidence
that we were lost and high [__]
but my white buddy he was smoking The
Joint Dave Dave it's the goddamn
[Applause]
cops I'm going to ask him for
directions
I said chip no chip don't do it it was
too late he was walking over there this
man was high [__] excuse
me excuse me sir touching them and [__]
excuse
[Music]
me need some information uh start
confessing things he shouldn't confess
I'm a little
high all I want to know which way is
Third Street the cow was like hey hey
take it
easy you're on Third
Street you better be careful go ahead
move it move
it that's all that happened that's the
end of the
story now I know that's not amazing to
some of you but you ask one of these
black fellas that [__] is [__]
incredible isn't it I'm saying a black
man would never dream of talking to the
police hat that's a waste of
weed
serious I mean I be scared to talk to
the police when I'm
sleepy [__] around get the wrong
idea oh my
God that [__] was on PCP
Johnson I had to use necessary Force you
saw
them no no no paperwork just just
sprinkle some crack on them let's get
out of
here that's how it is but at the time I
didn't think there was anything racial
about it I was just like man chip you
got [__] lucky you better be careful
but then another time me and Chip are
driving now I'm not driving chip is
driving and he's driving a little crazy
he been
drinking now I don't like like to let my
friends drive drunk but you know I was
smoking a joint I couldn't really say
[__] to the
guy and we get at a red light we stop at
a red light and the car pulls up next to
us and I'll never forget it chippy looks
at me he's all drunk and she's like
Dave I'm going to race
him I knew it was a bad
idea but I was high I tried to explain
to him it was a bad idea but all that
came out was well [__] sometimes you
got RAC I don't
[Applause]
know man that light turned green and
Chip took off zigzagging and [__] andno
cap pass other car I didn't even know it
was
racing then the police seen us and
pulled us over now you understand I'm
scared scared as [__] I mean come on the
car smells like weed been speeding this
man is [__]
drunk I was scared chip was not scared
at all it was weird he didn't turn his
radio down a it weird a little bit I
mean if you get pulled over wouldn't you
turn your radio down nobody want to get
their ass beat to a soundtrack and
[__] you know what I'm
saying chip had the music blasting we're
not going to take it
me said Dave just relax close your butt
cheeks
relax let me do the
talking you want to know what he said
it's almost exactly what he said I
couldn't believe it he says oh
oh sorry officer I
I didn't know I couldn't do
that I was [__]
shocked the cop said well now you
know just get out of here just get the
[__] out of
[Applause]
here she said okay I'll I will sir thank
you
what what's wrong with you
Dave I didn't know I couldn't do that he
said that was good wasn't
it because I did know I couldn't do
that I was
shocked I wasn't shocked at the audacity
I was just shocked because I would have
never thought to say that I don't think
any black dude would think to say that
because they know we know the
law every black dude in this room is a
qualified pargal and [__] he knows the
law if one of us even start to do
something wrong a old black man and pop
out of nowhere [__] don't do that
that's 5 to
10 watch
out we know the laws and the penalties
got chip didn't even know he couldn't
race I'm not saying I don't like police
I'm not saying that I'm saying I'm just
scared of them nothing wrong with
that sometimes we want to call them
to somebody broke to my house once it's
a good time to call him but
I house is too nice and ain't a real
nice house but they never believe I Liv
there be he's still
here oh my
God open and shut case
Johnson I saw this once before when I
was a
rookie apparently this [__] broke in
and hung up pictures of his family
everywhere well let's sprinkle some
crack on him and get out of
here oh you know that's that that's that
whole brutality thing is see that's
common knowledge man it was a time when
only minorities really knew about that
I'm not going to say why people didn't
believe us but you were a little
skeptical he a little skeptical I mean I
don't blame you and then Newsweek
printed he knew was the
truth and the Newsweek wife like oh my
God honey did you see this apparently
the police have been beating up Negroes
like hot
cakes it's in the main
issue I mean really how could you know
though how could anyone else know you
know I mean maybe you should have seen
something a little suspicious you think
it was like a little suspicious it's a
little suspicious every dead black
person in police find has crack
sprinkled on them I mean come
on come on man who gets shot and
sprinkles crack on themselves nobody
would do bam oh
oh I don't want to leave no
Mysteries but I'm a paranoid guy you
know that's how I am I am I'll be scared
to call 911 for anything even if it's
like a fire or anything because they
take those phone
calls I see the shows they tape them and
then they play them on television that's
[__]
up now I'll say anything if I'm scared
that [__] is private you know what I
mean what if I get killed and start
playing that 911 tape on the news I'm
dead I can't explain myself to my
buddies and
[__] we watching the news we have
register traing on on the scene
re what's going on out
there always takes a guy on the scene a
minute hi
Bob hi yes we just got hold of a copy of
Dave Chappelle's frantic 911 emergency
call remember viewers some of this
language is
disturbing
hello emergency
help help [__] they coming to
get
me just calm down sir where are you oh
oh I [__] on
myself I can't stop
crying they play that [__] 30 40 times a
day all my buddies will be in my funeral
looking at
me you know they [__] on themselves
right
saw it on the news died crying like a
[Applause]
[__] I'll be dead I can't defend
myself that's not a nice thing to do
that's not a nice thing to do I mean
it's a 911 tape how they expect you to
sound of course you're going to be
scared it's an emergency nobody calls
911 cool and relaxed that that [__]
would sound ridiculous hello
emergency
hi hey 911 how are
you yeah uh look there's a group of
hooded white men Gathering outside of my
house and it looks like they mean
business get out here
[__] I got to
go you guys trying and
hurry
it's too much pressure that's my problem
I can't I can't handle
pressure sometimes pressure make me talk
different I'm serious you ever have like
that social pressure you talk to
somebody who's fake and they make you
fake like they come to you like hey how
you doing you're like fine how are you
you're
like I don't even talk like
that I get sick of that
[__] I do it makes me sick sometimes
I'll talk crazy just to make myself feel
better youever do that and start talking
like crazy like ever hear this voice
man that's that's how bad guys used to
talk in the 40s in the old days see I
used I talk like that now all the time
but if somebody put the pressure on me
[__] it I got I got to cut
loose May the police pull me over I'll
talk
crazy son
son do you know why we pulled you over
n cuz I'm black see that's
right I do
it it's not illegal to talk like
that how do they know I don't talk like
that every day stop talking like that
stop talking like my
CER how I talk
say you got to make life interesting
like that cuz the [__] is
flimsy life is flimsy you think you
going to live for a but not going to
live
forever it's dangerous out here we know
what's going on I travel now you know I
used to think DC had the roughest
ghettos in the country nah
[__] I have seen some [__]
now oh there's some rough rough areas
outside of
DC yeah everybody should go to the
ghetto I was taken to the ghetto one
time that's the worst when you get taken
you're not expecting to go
usually you want to know when you go in
the ghetto like I'm going to see some
wild [__] I got to prepare myself I'm
going to see something
crazy when you're taking it's different
I had a limousine
driver it was after a show it was late T
night it was like 3:00 in the morning I
had a limine driver he's a nice guy
talking to me and [__] oh hey where you
from dog DC
word that's a rough City
man and the cell phone started ringing
hold on one second hello
oh what's up [__] what what the [__]
slow down what what the [__] no no no
[__] that [__] [__] it I'm on my
way
hey I got to make a stop real
quick at 3:00 in the morning and I
didn't know he was taking me to the
ghetto at first I started looking out
the window I was like what the [__] Fu
gun store gun store liquor store Gun
Store where the [__] you taking
me this don't look good he didn't say
[__] just pulled up in front of an old
rickety building that looked like a
project now I never been there before
I'm not sure if it was a project but it
certainly had all the familiar symptoms
of a
project a [__] crackhead ran this
way and then and then another one jumped
out a tree and
[Applause]
[__] I said I'll be right back and left
me took the keys with him and just left
me at 3:00 in the morning in front of a
project in a [__]
limousine this was not
good I was like man I got to look around
and see if I can see some landmarks and
figure out where I'm at might have to
escape on
foot now this is when I knew I was in a
bad neighborhood you only see this in
the worst neighborhoods remember it's
3:00 in the morning it's 3:00 in the
morning I look out the
window it was a [__] baby standing on
a
corner and the baby the baby didn't even
look scared he was just standing
there
I mean it made me sad it made me sad
really you know what I mean cuz I want
to help the
baby I was like I don't trust you either
I'm sorry click
click the old baby on the corner trick
he I'm not going to fall for that
[__] where is this nine dver you know I
st feeling bad as time goes by I start
feeling worse like man what is wrong
with me what the hell is wrong I scared
of a
baby and this baby could be in trouble
he might need my help I got to do
something but I wasn't going to get out
the
car I'm serious man I just cracked the
window a little
bit there's a old limousine I can roll
it
down
hey
baby baby go home man it's 3:00 in the
morning what the [__] are you doing
out the baby said I'm selling weed [__]
I said oh
[__] I wasn't expecting
that I'm S I had to buy two bags from
the com let me get two let me get two f
[Applause]
got back in the car and rolled me a
joint man that [__] was scary man every
once in a while like a crackhead would
come up to the car and look in the
window it's like Jurassic parking should
he be looking on the
car hey get out of here
[Applause]
crackie that baby was still standing
there man that's what then I start
feeling bad again yeah weed make you
feel guilty
sometimes man what is wrong with me man
I have bought weave from a from an
infant I can't condone this kind of
behavior what am I thinking I can't let
the fear ruin my
morals got to do
something hey
baby stop selling weed all right you got
your whole life ahead of you he said
[__] you [__] I got kids to feed I said
God damn
s and just at that very moment one of
the crackheads was running across the
street and got hit by a car I know it
was a hidden run the police did
it that's all right they springing some
crack on him and got back
up
yeah I've been seen that kind of [__]
man it's what it is they use the TV to
program us from a young age you ever
watch like a cartoon that she used to
watch me a little as an adult [__] is is
wild [__] some wild [__] I mean like I
was with my nephew we sitting there we
watching peepy the Pew I said to my NE I
said now pay attention to this guy cuz
he's funny I used to watch him when I
was
little and we watch your Pula Pew and
I'm old now I'm looking like good God
kind of [__] rapist is this guy like
take it easy
my nephew was sitting there cracking up
he see sometimes you got to take the
[__] like pppe like no
no
no I had to turn the channel real
quick I turn on Sesame Street I said oh
Sesame Street this is much better cuz
now he'll learn how to count and
spell but now I'm watching it as an
adult and I realize Sesame Street
teaches kids other things it teaches
kids how to judge people and label
people that's right they got a character
on there named
Oscar they treat this guy like [__] the
entire
show they judge him right in his face
Oscar you are so mean isn't it
kids yeah Oscar you're a grouch it's
like [__] I live in a [__] trash
can
I'm the poorest [__] on Sesame
Street nobody's helping
me then you wonder why your kids grow up
and step over homeless people get it
together
Grouch get a job
Grouch so don't even tell me how to get
to Sesame Street that is a terrible
place I wouldn't go there if I knew the
way who would want to live in a
neighborhood like that [__] six foot
pigeons walking
around
an elephant that's a
junkie H
Bird yeah that's right Snuffy hi bird
I'm sick I need some smack
bird can Cookie Monster with his eyes
popping out his head scam cookie cookie
cookie like e kind of cookies are you
talking
about chocolate chips don't do that to
people and then had the nerve to put a
pimp on there
they didn't come out and say he's a pimp
but I know a pimp when I see one they
called him the
count had a cape and
everything you that s pimping [__]
where is my
money you've been late four times I've
been
counting how many times must I smack you
before you act right one
two two smacks ah oh oh oh oh
oh that's the thing there so many stuff
there's so much stuff to worry about you
know the more you know the more you
don't know and
[__] you know like a lot of people be
telling me Dave you know you just got
relax and race to some thing we bugging
you too much I be thinking about it
sometimes shit'll happen you know a lot
of black people can relate to this have
you you ever had something happen that
was so racist that you didn't even get
mad you were just like God damn that was
RAC that was
racist I mean it was so blatant you was
just like
wow like it almost like it didn't even
happen to you was like a [__] movie
that was like he was watching
Mississippi Burning
wow that happened to me I I was in
Mississippi I was in Mississippi doing a
show and I go to the restaurant to order
some food and uh I say to the guy I said
I would like to have and before I even
finish my sentence he says the chicken
what the
[__] I could not believe it could not
believe that [__] this man was
absolutely right I said how did he
know that I was going to get some
chicken I asked him I said how you know
that how' you know I was going to get
some
chicken he looked at me like I was was
crazy come on buddy come on
buddy now everybody knew soon as you
walk through the goddamn door you're
going to get some chicken it is no
secret down here that blacks and
chickens are quite fond of one
another then I finally understood what
he was saying and I got upset I wasn't
even mad I was just upset I wasn't ready
to hear that
[__] all these years I thought I like
chicken cuz it was
delicious turns out I'm genetically
predisposed to liking
chicken said
why I got no say in the m i got ruined
chicken for me I'm scared to eat it in
public I don't I want somebody to see me
and say something you know what I mean I
be eating some
chicken
look at
him he loves
it just like it said in the
encyclopedia look how happy he
looks sometimes the world be too much to
deal with that show business be crazy
that's where the cultures really Collide
Show Business bring a lot of races
together sometimes it works sometimes it
don't this is one thing that happens
that's funny you know sometimes I'll be
on a business call right you know like
with with a lawyer or something you know
my lawyers be white and uh
and like we'll be on the call right and
they'll be like oh okay Dave we're going
to we're going to close the deal was
that fine with you I'll be like yeah
that's good for me great great you have
a good weekend Dave I'll be like all
right you too man peace oh all right
bye-bye
they don't know what to say right so
sometimes sometimes I'll make up [__]
that's not even
slain just to see how they handle it and
[__] it be the same business go all
right we're going to close the deal is
that fine with you Dave yeah sounds good
to me great you have a good weekend Dave
all right buddy zip it up and zip it
out
oh
all right bye
by sometimes you know sometimes racism
works out and black people's favor now
it doesn't happen often it happens very
rarely but when it happens it is [__]
sweet I'm serious
one time racism saved my life man I was
I was on a
plane I I was coming I was coming from
overseas and uh I don't know how this
guy got a machine gun on the plane but
he stood up man he said everybody get on
the [__] ground nobody look at my
face I started freaking out cuz he was
Chinese I was like why is he talking
like
that
was screaming and
crying I was the only brother on the
plane I thought I was the only brother I
looked over there was one other black
dude he was from
Nigeria I looked over at him he was
looking right in my face man he didn't
say two words to me he just looked at me
he was
like he didn't need to talk I know just
we was talking about I look right back
at him I was
like some white dudes on on the front of
the plane scen us they were like oh my
God I think those black guys are going
to try to save
[Applause]
us we were just
communicating that we understood the
situation we were both seeing the same
thing what we understood was
simple terrorists don't take black
hostages that's the truth I have yet to
see one of us on the news reading the
hostage letting
um they is treating us
good uh we all chilling and
[__] I like to give a shout out to Ray
Ray and big Steve and T some
Newport
you're not going to see
it terrorists are smart they know what
they doing there you know they
terrorists they know those black
people's bad bargaining
chips they call the White House hello we
have got five blood
hello
you be back in DC know nobody was
thinking man this is this is an election
year I'm going asking you your wife got
do you know who you're voting for
yet don't know do you now you see that
you see what just happened here let me
tell you something that is a cultural
thing he knows who he's going to vote
for he's just not going to tell
me
see I I've noticed that that is a
cultural thing white people do not like
to talk about their political
affiliations it's a secret you ever ask
white guy who's voting for hey Bob uh
Bob who you going to vote for Dave Dave
whoa whoa whoa who
who take it easy now take it
easy so anyway um I was [__] my wife
in her ass right
and and I mean it was something
else yeah yeah yeah yeah but but but who
are you voting for
Dave Dave come on with the voting trying
to tell about the [__] with my wife
you're asking me all these personal
questions they don't like to divulge
that information cuz it matters to them
black people talk about that [__] black
people openly talk about politics black
people openly talk about beating up
politicians and [__] if I see George
Bush I'll kick his [__] ass for
cutting my
Medicaid okay very sh
I we just say it but there's a reason
for that it matters more for it matters
more black people see see even when I
vote right which I don't but but but
even when I like think about like who I
would vote for right I don't even look
at their political policies I just look
at their
character you know what I'm saying now
you got to read no I'm serious you got
to read between
lines like you know you look at Clinton
and black people like Clinton cuz we've
seen him on the C I saw one thing on the
campaign Trail he he actually just
picked a black baby up and kiss him come
here you little [__] baby just kiss
him I said
mhm I like
that he did not hesitate or
nothing you see George Bush Jr he be
there
like I say I never vote for George Bush
Jr but I don't know George Bush Jr's
politics only thing I know about George
Bush Jr is that that guy sniffed cocaine
that's right now listen we cannot have
that [__] in the White House that might
be fine for a mayor but God damn it not
in the white
house not in the White
House you what I'm
saying
the stakes are too high in the White
House can't have no cokehead
president- he be selling nuclear secret
for 20 $30 and
[__] he be in meetings embarrassing
America come
on sign a treaty
baby I suck your dick like what
the Mr
res
Mr
President that is not how we do business
here
sir stop sucking the ambassador's
dick no let them
finish I will sign the
treaty there will be peace in Israel
finally I'd vote for Clinton again if I
could at least it's always
better
now again I'm not looking at his
politics don't know what his politics
are I'm just looking at his
behavior I understand that kind of
behavior I know a lot of dudes with them
shortcomings weed smoking fornicators
there a lot of
them I mean come on now let's let's be
honest let's let's be honest Bill
Clinton was not the first president to
do what he did now now let's just
just let's let's think back for remember
a guy named named Kennedy John F Kennedy
remember him he [__] Marilyn Monroe
matter of fact him and his brother Bobby
[__] Marilyn
Monroe and history doesn't talk about
that much you know why history doesn't
talk about that much because those two
pages in history are stuck
together
they they was getting it
on they were getting it
on I seen the tapes remember the tapes
you be singing on Nancy's party
stressing them out Happy
Birthday Mr
President [__] my family's
here
Clinton did the same thing but they
didn't do it like that because it's the
year 2000 he's busier than Kennedy was
he was a busy man Clinton did that kind
of thing the way busy men do it you know
what busy men do they [__] who's close
to
them I can tell that's what Clint was up
to look like just stuck his head out the
office door and [__] oh
boy you come here come here
I made my queena suck for my 330 come
on oh
boy he's probably looking at Kennedy's
picture and
[Applause]
[__] and in the top it off he lied which
I thought was just I thought that was
special I did man I know how he did I've
been accused of having sex with a girl I
did not have sex with before and let me
tell you something that [__] is
infuriating you ever go through that you
it'll make you crazy you be screaming at
your best friends I didn't touch that
[__] [__] I kill you [__] you [__] I
K you please believe me please believe
[Applause]
me Clinton didn't do it like that did it
Clint came out of the press conference
all relax shoulders all relaxed he in
all this trouble look like just got done
[__] or some
oh listen let me tell you something
America I don't think you heard me the
first
[Applause]
time I did
not have sexual relations with that
woman
Miss no
winsky know
did you
minut everybody know what that finger
smell like nobody
cares nobody car we all watch we was
disgusted but we kept watching the news
I know I did I was taping
it I at the crib like baby turn the
lights off the news is coming
on every week on 60 Minutes it was a
different girl accusing Clinton remember
Kathleen Willie came out she was upset
the
president called me into his office he
began massaging my breast slowly I'm
sorry and then he play placed my
hand on his
genitals Ed Bradley was
shocked was he
aroused I was at home like yeah was he
aroused
or and then Ed Bradley looked right in
the camera he said don't bust that nut
yet we'll be right
back oh man the news had never been so
good but there were no victims there
were no victims only one I feel sorry
for is that uh Linsky I feel a little
sorry for her don't y'all feel a little
sorry for her at
all God damn y'all come on now have a
hard that's a hard thing to be famous
for
man nobody want to be the most famous
[__] of all times and
[__] I feel bad for her not even the
women feel sorry for a little bit
ladies now that's
jealousy that's what that
is I mean come on y That's one dick that
that girl suck just going to haunt her
for the rest of her life long after she
spent that money up that's still going
to haunt her I know there's a lot of
women in here with at least one dick
they regret
and I bet you wasn't a president's dick
I bet you worked at Kenny shoes a
Safeway or some [__] like
that don't go judging her don't go
judging
her see we got to stop judging people
that girl was young and she made a
mistake that young girls make she wanted
to [__] a powerful man period that's as
far as she thought it through she wasn't
thinking about how powerful the
president was she have no wisdom older
woman woman would have helped everybody
older woman would have been in there you
know um you should lower
taxes
I'm a old of them would have sucked us
into
Utopia last thing I'm going to say about
it is this that he is a famous man I
have dreamt of being famous but I never
dreamt of being that famous I never
understood how famous a president was
would imagine if if somebody could suck
your dick and then they're famous you
understand what I'm
saying that's
crazy that's
crazy I mean no guy ever thought of that
there's nobody with a pickup line that
good and [__] they suck my dick there's
a future in it what oh that's it now get
out there and be
somebody go write a
book you're a qualified author now go
write a book
said I'm in the wrong business I should
be the president [__] I'm in the wrong
business see the only reason I want to
be president is cu I'm black that make
it too hot for
me I mean you know what I mean I think
it could be a black president one day
but you don't want to be the first one I
mean second or third that's fine but
that first [__] better watch out I'm
going to tell you that right
now too hot I mean I'd be the first
black president I don't think that
nobody would really really hurt me I'm
sure somebody want to hurt me me but I
don't think they touch
me cuz
uh cuz of my vice president will be
Mexican for a little
Insurance you know what I'm
saying you can shoot me if you want but
you're just going to open the Border up
so might as well leave me and vice
president Santiago to our own
devices ain't that right Santiago
see
Elon can
stay don't worry don't worry I don't got
no Elon
jokes all I'll say about Elon is thank
God it's CU cuz if he was Haitian you
would have never heard about his
AG if Alon if Alon Gonzalez was Elon
lumbo from Hai ready to push that little
rubber tube right back in the water
sorry fell all
full good
luck the only thing in our society that
bothers me the most is the way that men
and women don't get long no more that's
really what's bugging me about it men
and women just don't get along like I
hear women say this all the time I know
a lot of you sisters be like chivalry is
dead don't you don't y'all feel that way
like men aren't gentlemen
anymore
that's right chivalry is dead and women
killed
[Applause]
it there a fundamental difference in the
way we're going to see things we're not
going to see out ey on this issue we're
just not our test in life are different
a woman's test in life is
material a man's test in life is a woman
Now by test I mean that those are the
things that we desire men have nice cars
not cuz they like nice cars because they
know women like nice
cars that's how it goes cuz men are
hunters and the car is the
bait and the woman comes and says oo
nice Porsche gotch you
[__]
that's how it
is that's true come on now you go to a
woman's house their house be comfortable
as [__] women love comfortable
surroundings so men get comfortable
surroundings let me tell you something
if a man could [__] a woman in a
cardboard box he wouldn't buy a
house but that's still now where
chivalry got killed chivalry got killed
by the famous movement on the magazine
that got women going crazy because women
got too much advice about men from other
women and they don't know what the [__]
they talking
about it's true I see this [__] in the
in the magazines I don't read them but I
be seeing the cover I look at it be in a
grocery store fellas he look one of them
magazines like what is this and it's
going to cover 100 ways to please your
man by some
lady get out of
here ain't no 100 way that list is four
things long just suck his dick play with
his balls and then fix him a sandwich
and don't talk so much and never to
happen and then the magazines trick the
women the magazines St picking at your
self-esteem every page you turn you
start feeling fatter and uglier and you
feel like your clothes aren't good
enough and the magazines have you
forgetting how [__] beautiful you are
and that's what happens now look what
happens and then you forget how
beautiful you are and we all suffer if
[__] was a stock it would be plummeting
right now because you flooded the market
with it you're giving it away too
easy it's I'm just being truthful
I'm just
talking it would
plumet we be watching news today [__]
plumming it again on the
N Gold is up 10
[Applause]
points you can see it you ever you ever
have this happen this is how confusing
it is this this is the practical
application of what I'm talking about
like a guy be out it's happen to lot
guys you be out a club
all right you kicking with your boys and
and a girl walks by and man she looks
good she looks good not good in that
classical
way I mean you know I'm talking good
like she got half her ass hanging out
her
skirt her titties are all mashed
together popping out the top of her
turtleneck and
[__] and he with your buddy right you
with your buddies you got a couple
drinks in you and you see like this you
might try to talk to it might not come
out right I don't know what you say damn
look at them
titties the girl get maning oh uhuh oh
wait a minute wait a
minute just because I'm dressed this
way does
not make me a
[__] which is true gentlemen that is
true just because they dress a certain
way doesn't mean they are a certain way
don't ever forget it but ladies you must
understand that that is [__]
confusing just
EGS now that would be like me Dave
Chappelle the comedian walking around
the streets in a cop
uniform somebody might run up on me oh
thank God officer help us come on
they're over here help
us I'm oh
just because I'm dressed this
way does not make me a police
officer you understand what I'm
saying it's like all right lady
fine fine you are not a
[__] but you are wearing a [__]
uniform I'll tell you that [__] right
now little misunderstandings can happen
and in Men We misunderstand women a lot
you know we we always undermine their
feelings you can't do that to them you
can't
because see feelings are you see they
clapping feelings are very important to
women they are all important I'm just
learning this
[__] everything's based on how they
feel you can hear when they tell stories
you ever tell hear a man tells a story
it' be just facts who what when where
why it was me and Bob we was at Safeway
then that [__] Bob said this then I
punched that [__] and then I broke out
that's the
story that's the story women who tell
stories all these feelings and well
first of all you have to understand I
was on my period And I just talked to my
mother so I was feeling like like God
damn so many feelings what the [__]
happened get to it get to
it but I got to talk about
got to talk about them that's how they
always get me I've been sitting there
watching TV chilling and
[__] my old lady come up to me
David we need to
talk
[__] I don't say that out
loud that's how I feel
inside because I know every time we need
to talk we need to talk about some [__]
that I got to
do we don't ever have to talk about
anything she needs to
do she leaves me
defenseless I have to do what I have to
do David we need to
talk
nah don't do that to me David this is
serious ious stop talking in that voice
no
see I got to do this
see I complain but I'm happy I'm with
somebody I don't want to be I don't want
to be single I don't like that sometimes
you go to them single clubs you see too
much I was on the road one club and I
seen a uh I seen a thing they call a
thong contest
yes yeah I seen a thong contest SC yeah
it's some scandalous [__] all
right I couldn't get over that man cuz a
DJ you know I was dancing with a girl DJ
said everybody that wants to be in the
thong contest please report to the DJ
boo excuse
me they put on that song Some let me see
something them girls was going
off some of them pull their pants down
some them pull their skirts up all them
just shaking their butt some of them
didn't have underwear on they was just
[__] checking their
butt I mean really I was [__]
disgusting but I couldn't turn
away but no please for the squeamish
just plug your ears all right one of the
girls get so into it there's no cops
around right but she actually I'm sorry
to tell y'all this she spreads her butt
cheeks open she she spreads her butt
cheeks open in the middle of a crowded
disco right I was disgusted cuz I was
like 10 yards away from her I was like
oh my
[Applause]
God is that her is that her birth
canal oh it gets
worse good God Almighty is that a is
that a
baby I know that's gross it's gross cuz
it was a
baby it was the same baby from the
project she's like I snuck in the club
[__] I got that weed if you need
me just Pat on ass and I'll come
out hey guys thank you very
much love you
all make me Mo my
mind
up in here make me my up in up in
here